Lucas D. Batista

Mid. mobile developer

Summary

Passionate and well-qualified mobile developer with more than 5 years of experience. Working with Android and Flutter. Studying Agile, Clean Architecture, TDD, Design Patterns and Refactoring. I'm committed to the best way to produce high-quality softwares.

Know-how



Experience



Mid. Flutter developer at Kalunga S.A. August 2023 - Present



Mid. Android developer at americanas s.a. October 2021 - July 2023



Mid. Flutter developer at Megaleios June 2021 - August 2021



Jr. Flutter developer at Bean Softwares
March 2021 - June 2021



Jr. Flutter developer at Thalamus Digital July 2020 - June 2021



Jr. Flutter developer at MFIT Personal January 2020 - May 2020

Education



Computer Science at Univali February 2020 - Present



English at KNN Idiomas October 2020 - October 2022

Projects



iCut

April 2021 - Present



Unilovers

February 2022 - July 2023

Details

SC, Brazil

contact@lucasbatista.me

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

Skills

SOLID

TDD

Clean Architecture

Refactoring

Scrum

Cloud

Data Structures

Design Patterns

Languages

English

Hobbies

Hackathons, pair programming, teaching, code kata and reading.